Love is never still.
Benediction is a drama, history, war film directed by Terence Davies.
Poet Siegfried Sassoon survived the horrors of fighting in the First World War and was decorated for his bravery,
but became a vocal critic of the government's continuation of the war when he returned from service.
Adored by members of the aristocracy as well as stars of London's literary and stage world, he embarked
on affairs with several men as he attempted to come to terms with his homosexuality.
Siegfried Sassoon, played by Jack Lowden.
Siegfried Sassoon (Older), played by Peter Capaldi.
Robbie Ross, played by Simon Russell Beale.
Ivor Novello, played by Jeremy Irvine.
Stephen Tennant, played by Calam Lynch.
Glen Byam Shaw, played by Tom Blyth.
Benediction is a 2021 biographical romantic drama film
written and directed by Terence Davies.
It stars Jack Lowden and Peter Capaldi as the war poet Siegfried Sassoon, along with Simon
Russell Beale, Jeremy Irvine, Kate Phillips, Gemma Jones, and Ben Daniels.
The film was released in United Kingdom on 20 May 2022 by Vertigo Releasing
and United States on 3 June 2022 by Roadside Attractions.
The film explores themes of world war i, poet,
biography, lgbt, military hospital.
The tone is emotional.